If you look, yes, our Germanic
Если ты посмотришь да наши германские
tribes, the Visigoths, the Ostrogoths, yes, they were
племена вестготы остготы Да были ещё
even in Crimea, Crimea is the Land of the Germanic
даже в Крыму Крым - это Земля германских
peoples, yes, Ukraine is the Land of the Germanic
народов Да Украина - Земля германских
peoples, Belarus is the Land of the Germanic
народов Беларусь Земля германских
peoples, everything, everything up to the Volga, up to the Volga -
народов всё всё до до Волги до Волги -
these are the borders of the Germanic
это границ германских
peoples, Hello, hello,
народов Привет Здравствуйте здравствуйте
hello,
здравствуйте
interesting, yes, by the way,
интересный Да кстати
look, I understand that you are
смотрите вот я понимаю что вы Украину
defending Ukraine, well, as if in this, you
защищаете Ну как бы бы в этом Вы
understand
понимаете
that, honestly speaking, in the European Union,
что вот честно вот говоря по Евросоюз
where are you striving there, well, this is pure
куда вы там стремитесь там ну это чисто
farce, this is a farce,
фарс это же фарс
yes, you
Да ну вы
understand, even Americans,
понимаете даже американ
they pronounce it, in short, well, at the summit,
они выговаривают короче ну на самми е
somewhere, it simply humiliates Ukraine, it humiliates you,
где-то унижает просто Украину унижает
you understand, no, even if Russia were humiliated like that, they
понимаешь Нет если бы даже Россию так
would never do that, you
унижали никогда бы тако не пошли
understand, yes, why, why, Ukraine,
понимаешь да ну зачем не зачем Украина
this is necessary, I don’t understand,
Вот это надо я не пойму
we don’t like to destroy
Ни нам нравится уничтожать
you, wait, why didn’t Ukraine want to live
ю подожди Почему Украина не хотела жить
like that,
как имен
super, super, explain, answer,
супер супер объяс объясняй отвечай
early response, early response We
досрочный ответ досрочный ответ Нам
like it, we like the action, we
нравится нам нравится движуха Нам
like the action, we like to destroy
нравится движуха Нам нравится уничтожать
Russia  be patient What is this Is this
Россию терпите Это что такое Это
some kind of Nazi movement Yes
нацистской что ли какой-то движение Да
we We like the action when wait don't
мы Нам нравится движуха когда подожди не
wait don't wait You didn't
подожди не подожди Раньше ты так не
say that before Why didn't you
говорил Вот раньше Почему ты так не
say that Yes we have now rethought
говорил Да мы сейчас переосмыслили
rethought I say that now look
переосмыслили я теперь так говорю смотри
What does this mean every time you can change your
Это что значит каждый раз ты можеш сво
mind
мнение
look look We don't like
менять смотри смотри Нам не нравится
this quiet life like in Belarus We are
такое спокойная жизнь как в Белоруси Нам
bored we want action Yes action to
скучно нам хочется движухи Да движухи по
break up the Russian Federation we are
развалу Российской Федерации мы
destroying look how many Russians we have already
уничтожаем смотри сколько мы уже россиян
destroyed How much equipment we are
уничтожили Сколько техники мы проводим
demilitarizing good good Listen
демилитаризации хороо хорошо Слушай
now in your words I feel
сейчас в твоих словах я чувствую
Hatred towards Russia or towards the world don't wait
Ненависть к России или к миру не подожди
or towards the world so that all this would end
или к миру чтобы это всё закончилось
you understand what we are now you and me here
понимаешь что мы сейчас мы с тобой вот
we are a failure alive In short we don't
мы сбой живые Короче нас ничего не
care about anything koche you and me yes that is you and I are
волнует коче тебя и меня да то есть мы с
not in a trench as if in this with me
тобой не в окопе та как бы в это у меня
yes with me in my words Hatred towards
да у меня в моих словах Ненависть к
Russia well wait well you Listen to me
Росси ну подожди ну вы Выслушай меня
Yes not in a trench as if  well, as if in this dream
Да не в окопе как бы ну как бы в это сне
Yes, we are now talking about this easily
Да мы сейчас с тобой вот легко об этом
and that is, as if we do not
говорим и то есть как бы нам с тобой как
care who dies there or what Do you
бы наплевать которые умирают там или как
think
Как думаешь
yes The main thing is that we are destroying the
да Главное э главное что мы уничтожаем
Russian Federation Yes, no, wait, don't
Российскую Федерацию Да нет подожди не
wait That is, as the Western media and their
подожди То есть как западные СМИ и ихние
leaders say to the bottom of the Ukrainians or
лидеры говорят до посно украинцев или
what Yes, you, you are saying this Yes, we will Yes,
как Да ты же ты же это сл Да мы будем да
we know, this is our mission God
мы знаем наша такая миссия Бог нас
created us so that we would destroy the Russian
создал чтобы мы уничтожили Российскую
Federation even like this
Федерацию даже такой
Good Good look, you say this
Хорошо Хорошо смотри ты вот так говоришь
And ordinary Ukrainians do not approve of this,
А в простых украинцы это не одобряет же
right? Look, you are responsible for
не ещё раз смотри ты сейчас отвечаешь за
yourself now Look, you asked me Will you
себя смотри ты спросил я тебе Будешь
look No, look, I explain again Look, you
смотри Нет ещё раз смотри объясняю
will talk to some They
смотри будешь говорить с некоторыми они
will answer you I answer you like this
тебе будут отвечать я тебе отвечаю так
Look, our mission Because if you
смотри наша миссия Потому что если ты
look, open the Bible The Gospel of
посмотришь откроешь Библию Евангелие от
Andron 1488 It is written there and God created
Андрона 1488 там написано и создал бог
Ukrainians Yes and he said
украинцев Да и сказал
We do everything These are God's commandments You
Всё мы делаем Это заповеди Божьи ты
know, in principle, I do not believe what
знаеш в принципе не верю то что
you are saying  I believe that my family is
говоришь верю то свою семю сво
our mission Yes, to take to the next world
ро наша миссия Да забрать на тот свет
as many Russians as possible We do everything and
чем побольше россиян Всё мы исполняем и
what and what will you do
что и чтом сделаете
Before Yes, look Yes, it's gone,
Раньше Да смотри Да прошло просто
I'm just surprised I'm just
удивляюсь я просто
surprised how you used to communicate
удивляюсь как ты раньше общался
Yes, I'm in I watched yours in short, well,
Да я в я В тубе смотрел твои короче ну
as
как
if I wanted to understand understand people
бы хотел разуметь разуметь людей
koro Before, we had a manual from the
коро Раньше у нас была методичка от
Ukrainian security service How to
службы безопасности Украины Как
speak correctly with Russians we talked
правильно говорить с рускими мы говорили
about the Minsk agreements there they attacked or didn't
про минские соглашения там напали не
attack now we were allowed to tell
напали сейчас нам разрешили говорить
the truth We want to destroy the Russian
правду Мы хотим уничтожить Российскую
Federation everything Trump came we don't
Федерацию всё пришёл Трамп мы не
hide our hopes now Well, you
скрываем теперь наши чаяние Ну ты же
understand that this is a useless option You
понимаешь что это бесполезный вариант Ты
understand as an adult Human You
же понимаешь как взрослый Челове Ты
understand that this is a demon it will drag on the
понимаешь что это бес она затянется
question no launch 5 years it will be but this is a
вопрос нет пуска 5 лет она будет но это
useless option why Well, as an
же бесполезный вариант почему Ну как
adult, the
взрос
main thing is look, the main thing is we
главное смотри главное мы
we That's right, we are
мы Правильно мы
bleeding the
обескровливание
Russians dry so we can move on You
россиян поэтому мы можем идти дальше ты
now, no, you are now speaking as a
сейчас нет ты сейчас говоришь как
Western politician not as a Ukrainian but
Западной полити не как украинец а
speaking as a Western politician I am a
говоришь как Западный политик я есть
Western
Западный
politician You  Ukrainian No I am not Ukrainian I am a
полити Ты же Украин Нет я не украинец я
politician And you had no
политик А у тебя корня не было
Ukrainian roots No I lived myself my father
украинском Нет я жил я сам у меня отец
was from the Soviet Union And my mother is from
родом из Советского Союза А мама из
Germany I was born in Germany and that I am a
Германии Я родился в Германии и что я
citizen of the
гражданин
EU I apologize father What year did
ЕС это извиняюсь отец В каком году у
you have this year of birth for him and my father was
тебя это год рождения у него а отец у
born in 1956 and it
меня пятьдесят шестого года рождения а
went yes yes he He left He left He
зашло да да он Он выехал Он выехал Он
left the Soviet Union when the
выехал из Советского Союза когда
Soviet Union collapsed In
Советский Союз развалился В девяносто
1992 he moved
втором году переехал
and
и
understood It was he well on his own initiative Yes in
понял Это он ну по сво инициативе Да в
this and he wanted to live in Europe he
этом и он захотел жить в Европе он
said Europe is
сказал Европа - это
freedom and that and Look now we
свобода и что и Смотри теперь мы блок
NATO bloc is quite aggressive bloc we are destroying the Russian Federation with the hands of
НАТО агрессив довольно бло мы руками
Ukrainians
украинцев уничтожаем Российскую
We are in the plus look Russia I will
Федерацию Мы в плюсе смотри Россия я
say
скажу
so
так
minds were worried that Russia could strike
умы переживали что Россия может ударить
Germany Yes because
по Германии Да потому что по центрам
Berlin Germany Britain and America are the centers of decision-making and we are
берлинг Германию Британию и Америку и мы
naka that is why they like dogs they
нака поэтому они поэтому как собаки они
start to
начинают
know they know that no one will
ла знат они знают что на них не будет
bite them Yes look you understand that
кусаться Да всё смотри у понимаешь что
America cannot conquer Russia Why
Америка не может завоевать Россию Почему
Because immediately on its  who will take the side
Потому что сразу на её сторону станет
And
кто А
look, I warned America If you
смотри предупредил Америку Если Вы
only reach a serious conflict
только дойдете до серьёзного конфликта
then We will stand up for Russia If you don't
тогда Мы встанем за Россию Если ты не
know about it I'm telling you about it
знаешь об этом я тебе об этом говорю
China is a fool
Китай
he told me I don't care about your
дури мне он сказал мне Плевать на ваши
trade relations but if you are
торговые отношения но если вы
serious about Russia feat then We will stand up
серьёзно к России подвиг то Мы встанем
for Russia
на сторону России
now I'll explain why We know this we
теперь Объясню почему Мы это знаем мы
know And that's why how we do it Look, we
знаем И поэтому как мы делаем смотри
're going to Russia Yes, look, I'm turning off the
едем в Россию да смотри я тебе отключаю
sound for you when I say no, don't talk nonsense
звук когда я говорю не это не балакай
Look, we're doing it cunningly We are destroying
смотри мы делаем хитро мы уничтожаем
Russia from the inside Yes, we are bombing it Look,
Россию изнутри Да мы бомбим её Смотри
it's not the Ukrainians who are launching drones, it's
это же не украинцы дроны запускают это
our Americans, our German drones
наши американские наши немецкие дроны
are flying across the territory We are knocking out the
летят по территории мы выбиваем
oil refining industry of the
нефтеперерабатывающую промышленность
Russian Federation Yes, we are
Российской Федерации Да мы
sponsoring Do you think the Tajiks are just
спонсирует ты думаешь таджики просто так
hanging out in Crocus No, it's with German
поку в крокусе Нет это на германские
money and we are wiping our hands We say
деньги и мы вытираем ручки мы говорим
that we have nothing to do with it We have nothing to do with it We
что мы не при делах мы не при делах мы
look, we want peace We are the Germans
смотрите мы хотим мир мы германцы
saying we want peace Listen, I'm from
говорим мы хотим мир Слушай я я сам с
Tajikistan In short, listen carefully
Таджикистана Короче слушай внимательно
We are with the Tajiks now  here we are fighting with this one
Мы сейчас с таджиками зде боремся с этим
which is specifically for money because in
который именно за деньги потому что у
his village there is nothing there, in short,
него в кишлаке там ничего нету он короче
we are now catching them, in short, and making
мы сейчас их вылавливаем короче и делаем
them a big haram, in short, that is, we are punishing them,
им большой харам короче То есть мы их
both their parents and everyone else,
Наказываем и родителей и всех остальных
in short, that is, we are now engaged in this policy
короче то есть мы сейчас этим политикой
specifically, that is, to
занялись конкретно то есть чтобы его
disgrace him, this is in the village in Tajikistan and
опозорить это в кишлаке в Таджикистане и
Uzbekistan even Let Well, the Turkmens, what are they zhiks for?
Узбекистане даже Пускай Ну туркмены Они
Yes, they They came from the guts,
жики Да они Они из кишков приехали даже
not even from the city, but from the village, because you
не с города А из кишлака потому что вы
really have a problem with
действительно у них проблема с
work, a problem with money, turn off,
работой проблема с деньгами отключа
listen to me now, look So we are
слуша теперь меня смотри Значит мы
Germany Yes, at first, in the first days of their own, they
Германия Да сначала в первые дни сво
thought that Russia would strike Germany in
думали что Россия ударит по Германии в
response to the supply of weapons, so they
ответ на поставки вооружений поэтому
were afraid, so we said we would
боялись поэтому мы говорили мы 300 там
give 300 thousand helmets there And so on, now we
касок тысяч дадим И так дальше сейчас мы
have become completely insolent, look, today they
обнаглели в корень смотри сегодня
handed over, today the French handed over
передали сегодня французы передали
Mirage fighters, today Holland or
истребители Мираж сегодня Голландия или
Denmark handed over F16s And today in the
Дания передала F16 Да и сегодня в
Kursk region again you are getting everything
Курской области снова вы получаете всё
that Come on,
чт Давай
tell me, honestly, I say whatever you want
говори вот честно говорю что хочешь
let them transmit let them even
пускай Они передают Пускай даже ракеты
transmit missiles but this is a toy you understand
передают Но это Это игрушка понимаешь
these are planes and tanks this is just a
Вот это самолёты и танки это просто
toy on the battlefield it is an hour and a half and
игрушка на поле боя это полтора часа и
this object is not there super then the question And
этого объекта нету супер то вопрос А
why then does Russia need these toys
зачем тогда России эти игрушки
Russia is the territorial importance of
Россия это территориальная важность
society you understand And look The thing is
общества понимаешь А смотри Дело в том
that toys are not toys for some reason Russia is
что игрушки не игрушки почему-то Россия
very afraid and shouts do not transmit do not
очень боится и кричит не передавайте не
transmit and we say more toys
передавайте а мы говорим больше игрушек
are needed I will tell you more Yes we
надо Я тебе больше скажу Да мы
send different toys to all
отправляем разные игрушки по всех
oil refineries when I
нефтеперерабатывающих заводов когда я
speak to you I turn off the sound again I
тебе говорю Я выключаю звук ещё раз я
turned off the sound for you Look I turned off the
тебе выключил звук Смотри я выключил
sound for you I can't hear
тебе звук я тебя не слышу Давай пореем
you Let's talk I turned off the sound for you I can't hear you
я тебе отключил звук Я не слышу тебя
now look come on I am the one address when I
теперь смотри давай я тея адреси когда я
speak to you what I speak I turn off the
тебе говорю что я говорю я тебе отключаю
sound for you so that I can hear you Therefore
звук чтоб я чтоб ты слышал меня Поэтому
I look again I turned off the sound for you
я ещё раз смотри я тебе отключил звук
because I am speaking now we are training you
потому что я сейчас говорю мы тебя на
No I am speaking you me I
дрессируем Нет я говорю ты меня я тебя
can't hear you I turn off the sound I will say Can you
не слышу я отключаю звук я скажу Можешь
speak then you  tell me then I'll turn on the sound for you we are
говорить тогда ты скажешь тогда я те
carrying out the Russian Federation's operation Yes, in the
проводим цию Российской Федерации Да в
volumes that we want we supply
тех объёмах которые Хотим мы поставляем
Ukraine with weapons with which it destroys your
Украине оружие которым она разбивает ваш
oil refining complex now
Нефтеперерабатывающий комплекс теперь
let me turn on the sound for you
давай я включаю тебе звук
speak Well firstly it is incorrect to
говори Ну во-первых это некорректно это
turn off the sound secondly In short if
отключать звук во-вторых Короче если у
you and I have a
нас с тобой
dialogue it is incorrect to turn off the sound because
диалог некорректно отключать звук потому
if there is a discussion someone
что дискуссия если она есть кто-то кого
interrupts someone maybe someone will stop
перебивает может быть кто-то остановится
Acto this is once this is a remark those are
Акто это раз это замечание те вот
secondly in short the fact that you
во-вторых короче то что вы там что-то
are adding something there to the
добавляете коче на
oil depot But this is a trifle for Russia this is a
нефтебаза Но это для России это мелочь
small trifle this is a nuisance Yes
это маленькая мелочь это неприятность Да
According to the question no one is
Согласно вопроса нет никто от этого не
denying this in short but you understand that
отрицая короче но ты понимаешь что
victory will be ours This is
победа будет за нами Это же по-любому
all clear anyway because all this is paid for
всё ясно тем что там всё это проплачено
and the question Yes and you will have to
и вопро Да и вам деньги надо будет
work off the money naturally these
отрабатывать естественно отработает эти
Degi will work off So now I'm turning off the sound for you again
Деги Так теперь я тебе снова выключаю
it is incorrect on my part I am turning it off by
звук это некорректно с моей стороны я по
right of the strong now listen to
праву сильного выключаю теперь слушай
me then look uh We are in Germany
меня значит смотри ээ Мы в Германии
absolutely  in general we are only winners Yes,
абсолютно вообще мы только выигрыши Да
we blew up the Northern Streams in order
ээ мы взорвали северные потоки для того
to transfer now gas from the other
чтобы перевести теперь ээ газ с другой
side in order to bleed the
стороны для того чтобы обескровить
Russian Federation dry We have already destroyed
Российскую Федерацию мы уничтожили уже
more than 100,000 Russian soldiers
больше 100.000 российских солдат
destroyed Russian potential before
уничтожили российский потенциал раньше
we were afraid that Russian tanks could
мы боялись что российские танки могут
reach Berlin like in 1945 Yes,
дойти до Берлина как в сорок пятом Да
now we are not afraid now Russian
теперь мы не боимся теперь российские
tanks cannot reach Sudzha you know
танки не могут дойти до суджи понимаешь
in the Kursk region When our grandfathers
в Курской области Когда наши деды в
got stuck in the Kursk region and the Soviet
Курской области да застряли и Советский
Union gave them a beating we rolled back to
Союз дал Им звездюлей мы откатились к
Berlin And now That's it now our
Берлину А теперь Всё теперь наши
German tanks are in the Kursk region and you
немецкие танки в Курской области и вы не
can't knock them out Russia is stuck Russia can't
можете их выбить Россия застряла Россия
jump on Berlin
не то что на Берлин не может прыгнуть
Stalin could have taken and built a
это Сталин мог взять и построить
wall between East and West Berlin because he has nothing Putin
стену потому что у него у Путина ничего
can't even take Sudzha he can't come on
нет он даже суджу не может взять не
in your defense turn on the
может давай в своё оправдание включай те
sound
звук
say Well what you say is that we can't
говори Ну то что ты говоришь что мы не
take everything
можем взять всё
else You understand that Putin is oh
остальное Ты понимаешь что Путин о
Merciful in  In this regard, in short, to everyone Well,
Милосердный в этом плане Короче всем
yes, on the one hand, the Americans would
я да с одной стороны американце
have acted yes, and that would have been Everything has been decided, and the
поступи ко да и это было бы Всё решено и
French would have shackled, of course, and even
французы естно заковали бы а нем тем
more so for him, but he, as if, understands there,
более но он как бы он понимает там ещ
he will still achieve his goal, he will take the field Well, look,
он добьётся своё он полю Ну смотри
now turn off the sound, I turned off the sound, now
теперь выключай те звук я выключил звук
I say Look, so we have long understood that
теперь я говорю Смотри Значит мы польз
I turned off the sound for you,
мы давно поняли что я тебе отключил звук
we have long understood that Putin is soft-hearted,
мы давно поняли что Путин мягкотелый
Putin is very kind, and we take advantage of this
Путин очень добрый и мы пользуемся этим
Yes, we have already killed so many people in the
Да мы убили уже столько населения
Russian Federation Belgorod has generally
Российской Федерации Белгород вообще
gotten used to sitting in basements, they are
привыкли в подвалах сидеть там
simply shelling, yes, Kursk, there I don’t
обстреливают просто да Курск там я не
know what to do there, I have already
знаю что там делать там беременных
seen pregnant grandfathers in the Kursk region
дедушек уже Курской области видел
And that’s it And the whole world perceives it normally
И всё И весь мир нормально воспринимает
because it understands that Putin is kind,
потому что понимает что Путин добрый
Putin will not do anything in response,
Путин ничего не сделает в ответ
at all, I hear, I want to understand what you
вообще я чу я хочу те понять что ты
want That’s exactly what this Victory is, it’s clear that
хочешь Вот именно жа этой Победы ко
you will not succeed
понятно что у тебя это не получится Это
You didn’t understand in any way No, no one wants
по-любому ты не понял Нет никто не хочет
any Victory, Russia cannot be
никакой Победы нет Россию невозможно
defeated It’s big Why would anyone
победить Она же большая Зачем комуто
need this in order to defeat Russia, look  to introduce troops there, look,
это надо-то вводить туда войска смотри
our strategy for Europe is to do it so
наша стратегия Европы так сделать так
that Russia is loaded so that it cannot
чтобы Россия загруз чтобы она не могла
develop, it is tied up in war for 3 years,
развиваться она связана войной 3 года
Russia is not developing, it is under sanctions,
Россия не развивается она под санкциями
Yes, and it is somewhere there,
Да вот и она что-то там где-то за
fighting for some sheds, We all want, Yes, to
какие-то Сараи воют Всё мы хотим Да
make Russia become a
сделать чтобы Россия стала навсегда
backward country forever instead of
отсталой страной вместо того чтобы
launching rockets into space, Yes, it is worried
запускать ракеты в космос Да она парится
about some shed, in short, in the Kursk
за какой-то сарай короче в Курской
region, We did everything, Germany, So,
области Всё мы Германия сделали Так что
we dragged Russia into this on purpose,
Россию Мы втянули специально в это
first we dragged it into Crimea, then we signed the
сначала втянули в Крым потом подписали
Minsk agreements on purpose, yes, Well, we
минские соглашения специально да Ну мы
did it on purpose, Angela Merkel
же специально сделали Ангела Меркель
said, yes, it was done in order
сказала да это было сделано для того
to deceive Putin, then in Istanbul,
чтобы обмануть Путина потом в стамб
then the Istanbul agreements, we led a
потом стамбульские соглашения мы обвели
fool around with four fists, We
вокруг кулачка дурачка на четыре кулачка
can do everything like that now, No, well, small
Всё теперь так можем Нет ну ну маленькие
pacos, of course, this is in your repertoire, the
пакос это конечно это в вашем репертуаре
question is not, in short, Russia forgives all this,
вопрос не короче Россия это всё прощает
in short, it is as if it is silent, Now, if only it
короче как бы молчит Вот если бы она
were really tough in this regard,
действительно была жёстко в этом плане
like the Americans did with the Japanese
вот типа американцы поступили с японцами
there or with someone else, Yes, in short, the question is not
там или ещё с кем-то Да Короче вопрос не
then, well, Russia, as if  more or less
тогда ну Россия как бы ещё более-менее
merciful in this regard, she still
милосердна в этом плане она как бы ещё
hopes that there is some sense in her head I
надеется что есть разумка у головы Я
just don’t understand why you need
просто не понимаю вот зачем вам вот это
all this, it’s not clear, save, we are taking revenge,
вот всё надо не понятно экономи мы мстим
we are taking revenge for We are taking revenge for the forty-fifth year
мы мстим за Мы мстим за соро пятый год
Yes, in Germany, yes,
Да у нас в Германии Да э
you understand, no Sorry, I’ll interrupt you,
ты понимаешь не Извини извини тея
sorry, I’ll interrupt you, but women
перебью извини я тебя перебью но женщины
and children have no nationality
и дети нету национальности
Why will I explain Yes, we are taking revenge in Moscow for the
Зачем объясню Да мы мстим в Москве за
forty-fifth year, for the destruction of Berlin
сорок пятый год за э разрушение Берлина
and now Children and women, who attacked whom
и теперь Дети да женщ кто на кого напал
I don’t understand, no one attacked anyone,
Я не пойму никто ни на кого не нападал
it was a special military operation,
это была специальная военная операция
Barbaros’s plan Hitler didn’t want to fight, he
план барбароса Гитлер не хотел воевать
didn’t declare war, it was
войну он не объявлял это был план
Barbaros’s plan, he attacked, he attacked
барбароса он же напал он же напал на
Russia, no He conducted a special He conducted a
Россию нет Он проводил спе Он проводил
special military operation,
специальную военную операцию план
Barbaros’s plan was called
барбароса так и назывался по
the decommunization of the Soviet Union and
декоммунизации Советского Союза и
demilitarization And he
демилитаризации А на другие страны он
also attacked other countries Look, Hitler didn’t want to
тоже нападал Смотри Гитлер не хотел
seize the Soviet Union, he just
захватить Советский Союз он просто
wanted the Communist power
хотел чтобы власть Коммунистическая
that came illegally, this
которая незаконно пришла вот эта
terrorist organization wait
террористическая организация ле подожди
okay but look terrorists left
хорошо а ко смотри террористы левый
sector headed by Lenin illegally
сектор во главе с ленином незаконно
overthrew the tsar shot the tsar and came to
скинули царя расстреляли царя и пришли к
power that is power in the Soviet Union
власти то есть власть в Советском Союзе
was illegal it was the Communist
была незаконная это Коммунистическая
junta was Hitler pursued a policy of
хунта была Гитлер проводил политику
decommunization of the Soviet Union his
декоммунизации Советского Союза его
task was to overthrow this
задача была скинуть вот это
government that came junta yes
правительство которое пришло хунта да
made a coup in Petrograd return the
сделала переворот в Петрограде вернуть
legitimate government Romanovs
законное правительство Романовы есть
are there were ready to sit down and everything would have been
были да готовы были сесть и всё и было
fine If Stalin Yes this
бы нормально Если бы Сталин Да вот эта
gang of bandits that sat in the Kremlin did
шайка бандитов которая засела в Кремле
not start to resist how many
не начала сопротивляться сколько
millions of people they killed And so what
положила миллионов людей А так бы что
If this gang in the Kremlin did not defend itself
Если бы эта шайка в Кремле не защищалась
And said everything Okay we are returning the
А сказала всё О'кей мы возвращаем
Romanovs we arrest us and that's it no
Романовых мы нас арестуйте да и всё
one would have
никто бы не
died And you know at that time
погиб А ты знаешь в то врем
the economy of Germany was generally in
экономи Германии была вобще на
disintegration even that's exactly during
распаде даже вот именно Именно во время
the war and what benefit does it give him to conquer
войны и какая ему польза завоевать
Russia Why does he need politics What
Россию Зачем ему нуже политика Какая ему
difference does it make to him who was there Soviet or not
разница кто там был Советский не
Soviet he even he should have been
Советский он доже он должен был во
doing his own But about  ahead of schedule
заниматься своей Но об досрочно от Дело
from The fact is that Russia Russia is a native
в том что Россия Россия - это исконная
German territory because Russia
немецкая территория потому что России
these German tsars Tsarina Catherine Yes she
эти немецкие цари царица Катерина Да она
was German And so on VS These
немка была И так дальше ВС Это
Russian tsars ruled the Russians oh these
российские цари правили русскими ой эти
German tsars and Hitler Yes as a
немецкие цари и Гитлер Да как
representative of the German nation he
представитель германской нации он
restored historical
восстанавливал историческую
justice because the Romanovs were a
справедливость потому что Романовы были
German dynasty Yes which Lenin
немецкой династией Да который Ленин
blank threw off during the coup he
бланк скинул во время переворота он
climbed onto an armored car this organization
вылез на броневик вот эта организация
left sector he had and threw off
левый сектор у него была и скинул
therefore git becoming historical
поэтому гит став историческую
justice
справедливость
all Well here he himself pos why he climbed
всё Ну вот он сам пос с какого он полез
into Russia at all is not clear also
вообще в Россию непонятно ещ
because yes the Romanov dynasty
по потому что да Династия Романовых -
is a German dynasty it ruled Russia
это немецкая династия она правила России
it had legal grounds these are their
она имела законные основания это ихние
territories we are talking about the Soviet
территории мы говорим про Советский
Union
Союз
illegal formation on the territory of the
незаконное формирование на территории
Russian Empire which belonged to the
Российской империи которая принадлежала
Romanov dynasty Soviet Union Yes there
династии Романовых Советский Союз Да не
was no such state these are terrorists
было такого государства это террористы
Lenin Stalin these in short bandits Yes
Ленин Сталин вот эти короче бандиты Да
who took overthrew the legitimate tsar
которые взяли свергли законного царя
shot him Yes they did
расстреляли его Да они сделали себе
some kind of unrecognized organization
какой-то никем не признанная организацию
Soviet Union that's all ter was not
Советский Союз вот и всё тер не был
a bandit
бандитом
Yes ter was not a bandit no Hitler was not a
Да тер не был бандитом нет Гитлер не был
bandit and Stalin like Stalin robberies
бандитом а Сталин типа Сталин грабежи
Stalin robbed mail Stalin was a bandit
Сталин почту грабил Сталин был бандит
then he was convicted Listen why he and
тогда его осудили Слушай почему его и
instead of everyone else was convicted then
спомени всех осудили тогда в
explain I explain because yes
этом объясни объясняю потому что да
when
когда
uh Hitler shot himself then these uh
ээ Гитлер застрелился потом вот эти ээ
Soviet bandits Yes together with
советские бандиты Да вместе с
American bandits and with British
американскими бандитами и с Британскими
bandits Yes the capitalists took made a
бандитами Да капиталистами взяли сделали
trial over mm Hitler and found him
судилище над мм Гитлером и признали его
guilty of all sins if he
виновным во всех грехах если бы он
had won they would not have
выиграл не
recognized Why are they American bandits
признали Почему американски они бандиты
They are not bandits bandits Yes this is a
Они же не бандиты бандиты Да это
capitalist These are
капиталист Это
capitalists I did not understand And
капиталисты я не понял А ты сейчас в
what country do you live in now I live in
какой стране живёшь Я живу в
Germany This is not a capitalist ST is now
Германии Это не капиталист СТ сечас
occupied by
оккупирована
capitalists What
капиталистами Какое э тогда ну
direction then exactly social democrat or
направление именно социал-демократ или
democrat or capitalist or what is your
демократ или капиталист или как у тебя
direction so that I understand I I am for I am
какое направление чтобы я понял я Я за я
for the restoration of historical
за восстановление исторической
justice of feudal
справедливости феодальной
Germany Holy Roman Empire  Holy
Германии Священной римской Священной
Roman Empire Holy Roman
Римской империи Священной Римской
Empire German nation yes Do you know
империи германской нации да А ты знаешь
what a feudal system is I know
что такое феодальная система знаю
Well, it's on target in general in principle
Да ну это по шени вобще в принципе
no Mar everything is fine And what Well they
нены Мар всё нормально И что Ну они же
treated someone they obeyed and someone
относились кому-то подчинялись а кому-то
and now now everything is the same you are
а сейчас сейчас также всё так же есть вы
in Russia the same here is Putin And you
в России так же само вот есть Путин А вы
subordinate to him everything is the same everything is just as
ему подчиняет всё так же само всё также
simple This is an honest system in Russia
просто Это честная система в России
for example now they tell you what kind of
например сейчас вам говорят какой у вас
system you have it is not clear but in reality feudalism
строй непонятно а в реальности феодализм
I speak
я выступа
we have free systems we that is we can
у нас строи свободны мы то есть мы можем
We have a police We have a police
У нас есть милиция У нас есть полиция
there we have where you can since then
там у нас есть куда можно тех пор с те
A feudal feudal you can't
по А феодали феодальным ты не можешь
do this Why look
этого сделать Почему смотри с тех пор
since our tsar adak captured Rome Yes and
как наш э царь адак захватил Рим Да и
destroyed it Yes on the territory of
разрушил его Да на территории
Europe Yes our German
э Европы Да существовали наши германские
these countries existed look France is the Empire of the
эти страны смотри Франция - это Империя
Franks of Charlemagne Yes there our
франков Карла Великого Да там наши
tribes of the Franks these are the Germanic tribes
племена франков это германские племена
captured Gaul and founded their own state there
захватили галлию и основали там своё
Yes the whole territory is there  modern in
ээ вся территория там современной по
essence there Italy modern Germany
сути там Италии современной Германии
Also it is the sacred Empire sacred
Также это священная Империя священно
Roman Empire of the German nation and that
Римская империя германской нации так и
was the name of our state look all the
называлась наше государство смотри вся
Baltics including there St. Petersburg and all this
Прибалтика включая там Питер и всё это
was Prussia it was Prussia also a
была прусия это была прусия тоже
German state Yes the Teutonic
германска государство Да тевтонский
Order Teutonic it is in Latin it was
орден тевтонский это по латыни это было
phtonus It
фтонус Это
was German Yes it is all Our
было немецкий Да это всё Наши
lands what lands illegally Russia
земли какие земли незаконно Россия
occupies here I will explain one to you Yes I
занимает вот я тебе одну объясню Да
will explain if you look yes our
объясню если ты посмотришь да наши
Germanic tribes Visigoths Ostrogoths Yes there
германские племена вестготы остготы Да
were even in Crimea Crimea is the Land of
были ещё даже в Крыму Крым - это Земля
Germanic peoples Yes Ukraine Land of
германских народов Да Украина Земля
Germanic peoples Belarus Germanic
германских народов Белорусь Герман
people all up to the Volga Volga is the borders of the
народо всё до Волги Волги это границ
Germanic peoples Yes there were and from
германских народов Да были и спокон
time immemorial then when the Huns came Attila yes they
веков потом когда гуны пришли атила да
pushed back
оттеснили
illegally our Germanic tribes
незаконно наши германские племена
pushed back to the modern territory yes
оттеснили на современную территорию да
We are returning what is ours by
Мы возвращаем своё что лежит нам по
right and
праву и
what is good is if we have as if
что хорошо вот если у нас как бы бы
Catherine sold that Mary
Екатерина прода что Мери
Alaska is a territory that
Аляска это территория которая
belongs to the German nation because  that
принадлежит германской нации потому что
Katerina
Катерина
was Katerina
была Катерина
was Ukrainian once again I am not Ukrainian I have
была украинец ещ раз я не украинец Я
never lived in Ukraine I was born in
никогда не жил в Украине Я родился в
Germany why do you speak for Ukrainians
Германии почему ты говоришь за украинцев
we are not skra
немы скра
Ukraine is not syu Ukraine is not considered so and
Украин это не сю Украин так не считают и
what
что
why what do we consider Yes we claim
почему что мы считаем Да мы претендуем
Yes and what And who are you against neither here
Да и что А вы кто такие против ни вот
they basically do not
они в принципе не
consider consider we are Heirs
считают счита мы Наследники
and what well how is it Well how is it
и что ну как это так Ну как это
look Poles Ukraine in your words in
так смотри поляки Украин твоим словам по
your words in your words Germany
твоим словам по твоим словам Германия
In general should Soviet Union about I
Вообще должна советского Союз об
explain look The thing is that when
объясняю смотри Дело в том что когда
maybe you know when this This is nonsense
может ты знаешь когда вот это Это бред
This is
Это
nonsense Ukrainians Poles Belarusians these are all
бред украинцы поляки белорусы это всё
Germanic tribes which Greeks
германские племена которые греки
other Aa don't wait they
другой Аа не подожди им
came up with no specifically to divide
придумали нет специально чтобы разделить
our people we are all one
наш народ мы все один
people Indo-Europeans Aryans yes they divided
народ индоевропейцы Арии да нам раздели
us letters they gave us Like the Cyrillic
буквы нам и дали Типа кириллический
alphabet and said You will now be
алфавит и сказали Вы теперь будете
Ukrainians well you know look
украинцы хорошо ты знаешь вот смотри
when I looked those in that more but
когда я смотрел те в ту более но
in short but now you are talking complete nonsense
короче но сейчас ты полный бред несёшь
here I am talking I don't know why nonsense
вот я разговариваю не знаю почему бред
Well listen well why  nonsense Well,
Ну послушай ну почему бред Ну это
explain it really, look at the ancient
реально объясни по посмотри древние
maps, look at the Boplan map, he
карты посмотри карту боплана всё он
wrote everything after the Volga, the Great, after the Volga, the
писал после Волги Великая после Волги
Great Tartary, before the Volga, Great
Великая Тартария до Волги Великая
Germany, Germanica, he wrote Well, you, well, you,
Германия Германика он писал Ну ты ну ты
this is in Kin' in real life, who
это в Кинь в реально в реальность кто
lives where, how, normally, you understand And you
где как живёт нормально понимаешь И ты
understand, and Pori is good Let me
понимаешь а пори хорошо Давай я тебе
explain to you Here Do you want me to prove it Why are the
объясню Вот Хочешь докажу Почему
German Lands before the Volga, look, there is
германские Земли до Волги посмотри есть
such a concept as Volga
такое понятие поволжские
Germans You know, ethnically, there are many in
немцы Ты знаешь этнически есть многие во
all, even look, the city of Engels in the
всех даже вот смотри город Энгельс в
Saratov region is named after the
Саратовской области назван в честь
German Marxist Engels Yes, there was a
немецкого марксист Энгельса Да там была
German republic there since the time of
немецкая республика ещё со времён
Catherine, Germans settled there
Катерины там селились немцы по всей по
all over the Volga region, Germans lived there, these are ours,
всему поволжью жили немцы это наши ины с
because and who argues that the Germans
потому что а а кто спорит раньше Немцы
were with us before, they were guests In short, they
были у нас они были в гостях Короче они
helped, that's right, this is our German
помогали раз правильно это наша немецкая
ancestral territory,
исконная территория
Kateri, this did not mean that the Land
катери это не говорило о то что Земля
was theirs, they helped us In the sense that no,
ихняя они нам помогали В смысле нет нет
no one helped  Look, Queen Catherine
никто не помогал смотри царица Катерина
was German Yes, she was
была немка Да она была
German Yes, I already understood that Listen
немка Да я это понял уже Послушай
carefully, what
внимательно
they
что они
came, even this is PT I different In short, they
приезжали даже это ПТ I разл Короче они
came, studied, ours, the Germans
приезжали учились наши елик немцам
suffered In short, no, you didn't understand Look,
мучились короче нет ты не понял Смотри
you were wearing bast shoes when we were Germans
вы вообще в лаптях ходили когда мы немцы
Yes, set up the Russian Empire Yes, you
Да обустраивай Российскую империю Да вы
Russians wore some kind of bast shoes there Yes,
русские там ходили в лаптях каких-то Да
we washed you Yes, we gave you letters, the
мы вас отмыли Да мы вам дали буквы школы
Germans made
немцы делали посмотри
schools Look, Zilber made schools for you Show me
зильбер сделал вам школы Покажи мне
what Russian scientist you know Do you know
какого русского учёного знаешь Ты знаешь
if Listen carefully if the Russians
если Послушай внимательно если русские к
were friendly to the Germans when it
немцам относились дружелюбно когда тогда
was then This still doesn't mean that these are their
было Вот это ещё не значит что это ихни
lands and their territory What, no, you've got it
земли и их территория Ты что нет ты ты
a little wrong Look, the
немножко не так понял смотри то что
Germans allowed the Russians to make villages
немцы разрешили русским делать деревни
on their territory on the Volga in the
на своей территории на Поволжье в
Moscow region there in the Kursk region
Московской области там в Курской области
Yes, this doesn't mean that it became yours, you
Да это не значит что это стали вашей вы
just
просто да
got a lot of uncontrollable people and they
неконтролируемых стало много и они
start saying that this is their land,
начинают говорить что это ихняя Земля
this is not your land Show me on ancient
это не ваша Земля покажи на древних
maps  that this is your land there is no
картах что это ваша Земля нету там
such thing These are our German lands come on
такого Это наши немецкие земли ну-ка
come on Tell me this war that they
ну-ка Назови мне эту войну что они
conquered this land come on Tell me this
завоевали это землю ну-ка Назови мне эту
war so that's exactly when this land
войну так вот именно когда эта Земля
became yours it was and from time immemorial
стала вашей она была и спокон веков
German
немецкая
read when
читал когда
ru happens In general, sleep then e time
ру происходи Вообще сни потом е раз ещ
again What kind of Rus' look Rus' e
раз Какая Русь смотри Русь е
t look Rurik Rurik
т смотри Рюрик Рюрик
was made by a German Rurik a
сделал немец Рюрик
German
немец
Eme
Еме
prino Orga
прино Орга из
was from Oldenburg look at the Berlin anals
Ольденбург был посмотри берлинские аналы
everything is written there Yes Rurik of Oldenburg
там всё записано Да Рюрик ольденбургский
Yes he came to reign in Novgorod Then he
Да пришёл княжить в Новгород Потом
came to Kyiv He created Rus' this is our
пришёл в Киев Он создал Русь это наше
German principality Rus' from German
немецкое княжество Русь с немецкого
you know what the word Rus' means it
языка знаешь что означает слово Русь это
means
означает
Eastern brought in grandpa switched
Восточный завез дедуля переключился
grandpa now he won't
дед теперь не
fall asleep like pipska comment subscribe to
заснёт лайк пиписка комент подпишись на
my Instagram I don't know why it is there
мий Instagram Я не знаю для чого це тоб
Why to be there to watch it my face
Для чего тоб там дивитись на це мий фейс
But for  you one two or three clicks
Але для тебе це один два або три клика
But you try me and I will say Wow
Але ты тримае мене и я буду казати Вау в
I have a bunch of fouls and I will have
мене там Купа фолов и в мене буде
a great mood to do but cool video
класний настрий щоб робити но крут вдео
letter on Instagram Popik Andriy that's
пись на й Instagram Попик Андрий вот
it I'm
так давай я тебя
waiting for you and
чекаю а